Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional materials, 1934-1958; Accession 2009-M-051
  - President Roosevelt, President Lebrun, Hon. William C. Bullitt, Hon. Laboulaye, Hon. Ickes, and others, fiftieth anniversary of the Statue of Liberty [commerically-produced], 1936 October 28; 9 phonograph records (78 rpm) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Broadcast originally on stations WEAF and WNYC, New York City.
    - Preservation master, 14
      - Use copy, 1 compact disc (Audio CD) (Box 3.2U)
  - Inauguration solennelle du monument Franco-Américain à Versailles, 1937 October 6; 7 phonograph records (78 rpm) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes speeches by M. Henry-Haye, Maréchal Pétain, General Pershing, William Bullitt, and M. Campinchi. Commercially produced.
    - Use copy, 1 compact disc (Audio CD) (Box 3.3U)
  - Ambassador Bullitt, National Broadcasting Company, Inc. (Blue Network), 1940 August 18; 2 commercially produced acetate phonograph records (33 rpm). (Box 4)
    Two records of a three-record set.
  - Computer files (Box 5–7)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Additional materials, Circa 1900-1993; Accession 2014-M-013
  - Bullitt, William C.
    - Correspondence, 1946-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1939-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Writings, drafts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Diplomatic papers
      - Weekly Report on Matters Related to the Allied and Neutral Countries of Western Europe, 1918 June 5-October 28 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
      - Weekly Report on Matters Relating to the Central Powers, 1918 January 21-April 8 (Box 2, Folder 7-10)
      - Supplement to Confidential Report on Matters Relating to the Central Powers, Number 42, April 22: Prince Lichnowsky's Memorandum, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Nos Garrigues et les Assemblées au Désert: Église de Nimes, sous la Croix, 1685-1792, by Albert Doumergue, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Bound volume presented to Bullitt as American Ambassador to France, 1937.
  - Bullitt, Anne Moen
    - Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Horse breeding papers, 1953-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Play programs, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Wedding invitations, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Artwork, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Oversized material.
  - Brewster, Daniel - Senate campaign pamphlets and correspondence, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bryant, Louise
    - Genealogy papers, 1906-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photographs
    - General, Circa 1930-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bullitt, William C., Circa 1900-1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bullitt, Anne Moen, Circa 1930-1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bullitt family, Circa 1900-1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Brewster, Daniel, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Paris, 1936-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Oversize, Circa 1900-1960s (Box 6, Folder 1-3, Box 7)
  - Unidentified film, Undated; 1 (Box 8)
- Additional materials, 1939-05-27; Accession 2017-M-006
  This accession consists of a May 27, 1939 copy of L'Illustration magazine, in which magazine reporters wrote about a Rouen, France commemoration of the death of Joan of Arc. Bullitt's photograph is on the cover of the magazine as he spoke at the ceremony.
  - L'Illustration magazine, 1939-05-27 (Box 1, Folder 1)